UCLA Foundation. Financial statements, minutes of meetings, and reports. 1967-1992. UARC.0664
UCLA Library Special Collections
UCLA Foundation. Financial statements, minutes of meetings, and reports.
1967-1992
UCLA Library Special Collections
UCLA Foundation
UARC.0664
14.8 Linear Feet (37 boxes)
Record Series 664 contains the financial statements, minutes of meetings, and reports of UCLA Foundation generated from 1967-1992.
Access
COLLECTION STORED OFF-SITE AT SRLF: Open for research. Advance notice required for access. Contact the UCLA Library Special Collections Reference Desk for paging information.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9934670593606533
Scope and Content
Record Series 664 contains the financial statements, minutes of meetings, and reports of UCLA Foundation generated from 1967-1992.
This is an active record series; additional University records are expected to be added.
- The UCLA Foundation - minutes, financial statements, reports., 1979-1980. (Box 1)
- The UCLA Foundation - minutes, financial statements, reports., 1978-1979. (Box 2)
- The UCLA Foundation - minutes, financial statements, reports., 1977-1978. (Box 3)
- The UCLA Foundation - minutes, financial statements, reports., 1990-1991. (Box 4)
- The UCLA Foundation - minutes, financial statements, reports., 1990-1991. (Box 5)
- The UCLA Foundation - minutes, financial statements, reports., 1990-1991. (Box 6)
- The UCLA Foundation - minutes, financial statements, reports., 1983-1984. (Box 7)
- The UCLA Foundation - minutes, financial statements, reports., 1983-1984. (Box 8)
- The UCLA Foundation - minutes, financial statements, reports., 1982-1983. (Box 9)
- The UCLA Foundation - minutes, financial statements, reports., 1982-1983. (Box 10)
- The UCLA Foundation - minutes, financial statements, reports., 1975-1976. (Box 11)
- The UCLA Foundation - minutes, financial statements, reports., 1976-1977. (Box 12)
- The UCLA Foundation - minutes, financial statements, reports., 1974-1975. (Box 13)
- The UCLA Foundation - minutes, financial statements, reports., 1973-1974. (Box 14)
- The UCLA Foundation - minutes, financial statements, reports., 1972-1973. (Box 15)
- The UCLA Foundation - minutes, financial statements, reports., 1971-1972. (Box 16)
- The UCLA Foundation - minutes, financial statements, reports., 1985-1986. (Box 17)
- The UCLA Foundation - minutes, financial statements, reports., 1985-1986. (Box 18)
- The UCLA Foundation - minutes, financial statements, reports., 1970-1971. (Box 19)
- The UCLA Foundation - minutes, financial statements, reports., 1987-1988. (Box 20)
- The UCLA Foundation - minutes, financial statements, reports., 1987-1988. (Box 21)
- The UCLA Foundation - minutes, financial statements, reports., 1991-1992. (Box 22)
- The UCLA Foundation - minutes, financial statements, reports., 1991-1992. (Box 23)
- The UCLA Foundation - minutes, financial statements, reports (2 volumes)., 1987-1988. (Box 24)
- The UCLA Foundation - minutes, financial statements, reports., 1967-1968; 1968-1970. (Box 25)
- The UCLA Foundation - minutes, financial statements, reports (2 volumes)., 1989-1990. (Box 26)
- The UCLA Foundation - minutes, financial statements, reports (2 volumes)., 1991-1992. (Box 27)
- The UCLA Foundation - minutes, financial statements, reports., 1984-1985. (Box 28)
- The UCLA Foundation - minutes, financial statements, reports., 1984-1985. (Box 29)
- The UCLA Foundation - minutes, financial statements, reports., 1981-1982. (Box 30)
- The UCLA Foundation - minutes, financial statements, reports., 1980-1981. (Box 31)
- The UCLA Foundation - minutes, financial statements, reports., 1981-1982. (Box 32)
- The UCLA Foundation - minutes, financial statements, reports., 1986-1987. (Box 33)
- The UCLA Foundation - minutes, financial statements, reports., 1986-1987. (Box 34)
- The UCLA Foundation - minutes, financial statements, reports (2 volumes)., 1988-1989. (Box 35)
- The UCLA Foundation - minutes, financial statements, reports., 1988-1989. (Box 36)
- The UCLA Foundation - minutes, financial statements, reports., 1989-1990. (Box 37)